# Ian Fleshman-Cooper

Kirkland, WA 98033 | Phone: (425) 495-3453 | Email: <a href="mailto:ian.fleshmancooper@gmail.com">ian.fleshmancooper@gmail.com</a>

LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/ian-fleshman-cooper/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/ian-fleshman-cooper/</a>

Portfolio: https://ianfleshmancooper.com

#### **Summary**

Experienced technology professional with a decade of dedicated service in the field of education. My extensive skill set spans support services, project management, troubleshooting, content creation, technical writing, and effective teaching and training. My commitment is to foster a growth mindset, elevate support for customers, ensure optimal learning experiences and workplace efficiency for others, as well as to infuse creativity into every aspect of my work.

#### **Technical Skills**

- Proficient in MS Office and G-Suite
- Atlassian Confluence, IIRA
- Canvas LMS
- Graphic Design: Figma / Adobe Create
- Salesforce Certified Administrator (SCA)
- Web Development: JavaScript, CSS, HTML, SQL, Node.JS, React.JS, MongoDB, GitHub, Heroku

### **Key Strengths**

- Continuous Learner
- Technical Writing
- Project Management
- Content Creation (Web sites, Videos, Graphic Design)
- Management System Administration (CRM, LMS, CMS)
- Technical Issue Resolution
- Lesson Planning
- Teaching / Training
- Team Collaboration

#### **Education**

**Full-Stack Web Development | Professional and Continuing Education:** University of Washington – Seattle, WA | 2021

24-week intensive program gaining technical programming skills in web development, as well as going in depth in learning UI Design, algorithms, efficiency, and data structures.

**Bachelor of Arts in Mathematics and IT:** Northwest University - Kirkland, WA | 2020 Summa Cum Laude – Annual Dean's List

### **Experience**

## Technology Support Analyst Seattle Pacific University

2023 – Present

Seattle, WA

- Lead projects addressing technology support needs, including system deployments and classroom technology support, while also providing tier 2 and tier 3 assistance to Helpdesk technicians.
- Develop comprehensive training materials and documentation for internal and external users on a variety of technologies. /Technical Writing and Content Creation
- Manage support cases and streamline communication through Jira.
- Utilize Microsoft products (Teams, Outlook, Entra, Sharepoint) and AI technologies (Microsoft Copilot, Gemini, ChatGPT) to optimize workflow efficiency.

## Digital Learning Specialist Monroe School District

2021 - 2023

Monroe, WA

- Developed and taught comprehensive Computer Science curriculum covering digital citizenship, coding, robotics, and computational thinking for K-5
- Administered Learning Management Systems (e.g., Canvas, Skyward) to track student progress and provide learning resources
- Facilitated technology integration and training for staff and faculty, improving workflows and efficiency in their work

# NPP Student Support Specialist

2018 - 2021

#### **Northwest University**

Kirkland, WA

- Guided students through the advising process to achieve their higher education goals
- Represented as advising representative for database updates to develop more efficiency within the advising support process
- Lead and trained new employees and students on how to utilize university software and learning platforms
- Gained proficiency in Salesforce, Excel, MS Access, PowerCampus, Microsoft 365, Teams, and Zoom for data management and communication
- Utilized Salesforce, Teams, and Office 365 to communicate with students daily to assist with a variety of academic advising related concerns and questions